We will now resume the match.
What's up with Razor's Nenbeasts? They're vanishing.
He drew back the aura he dispersed, so this next throw will show us his true power.
What's up with Razor's Nenbeasts?
We will now resume the match.
世界は君の輝きを奉ってる。
大地を踏みしめて、君は目覚めていく。
天使の微笑みで、連れ出して。
始まりはいつでも、波索大さ。
何度でも、勝ち上がれ。
The match begins once again.
Ghosn plans to take possession of the ball from Razor, but how?
I didn't think I'd need to use this.
I haven't felt this good in a long time.
Wait, straight up?
Then does that mean...
He's gonna spike it?
Hey, over there!
Wait, they're going to...
Merge!
I see what you're trying to do!
This battle determines...
The winner!
That's their strategy.
Ghosn stops it.
Hisoka traps it.
And Killua braces it!
They did it!
They stopped the ball!
Way to go!
I gotta give them credit.
Their skills prevailed over my power.
And it seems to me that the key to their success was that boy, Killua.
Ghosn focused all of his aura in his hands to catch the ball.
The concentration and focus that it took to pull that off are commendable.
The moment it reached Ghosn's hands, Hisoka enveloped the ball with his ability so Ghosn wouldn't drop it.
Had his technique been anything short of perfect, it's safe to say that the ball would have bounced off.
And Killua.
He was stuck between them, acting as both cushion and brace, balancing his aura between offense and defense.
If the aura around his body had been too weak, he would have failed to work as a cushion, and all three of them would have taken major damage from the ball's impact.
On the other hand, if he hadn't used enough aura on his legs, he would have failed to act as a brace, and the ball would have knocked all three of them outside of the court.
That required precise distribution of aura between his body and legs, leaving a margin of error of less than 1%.
That's a feat which demands both experience and skill.
But Killua overcame his inexperience with his prodigious insight, allowing him to perform such a difficult task.
What incredible talent! I didn't reach that point myself until I was in my late twenties.
I have to win before they merge. After they attack, I'll have my opening.
If I time it right, they won't be able to move into position.
Gon's throw is powerful. That much is painfully obvious.
But now, I have the power to catch it without having to worry about being bounced back.
And then, I can pick them off one by one.
I need more power.
More.
More!
He wasn't using his full strength before?
Is he?
But how?
How?
He's a monster.
You should be proud, Jin.
This kid's your son. There's no doubt about it.
Hey, Killua. I'm gonna give it everything I've got.
You better. Or you'll hear about it from me.
Now, show me Rock!
John!
Ken!
Rock!
Ha!
Stronger than I thought, but I can catch it.
However, at that speed, the Force will definitely push me out of bounds.
So catching it's not an option, but I can't shy away either.
Come on!
He's bumping it again?
Hisoka's just gonna grab it, moron!
You sure about that?
That depends...
On the direction of the bump!
He bounced it right back!
Go! Try to dodge it! You'll still win!
No way! He'll never dodge!
Because that isn't how he wants to defeat me!
I've learned that much about him in this match!
Huh?
He passed out? Of course he did.
He used up every last ounce of his strength with all that aura he expended.
You can take pride in this. You've won, Gon.
Not quite yet.
Huh?
What the hell are you doing?!
The win must be... flawless, right?
Right?
Whoa!
He bounced it back again!
How fun!
Are we going to exchange volleys?
Endurance it is!
The ball is stuck!
Bungee gum contains the properties of both rubber and gum, you see.
Catching the ball while the body is touching outside the court is illegal!
Razor is out!
Which means the winner of the match is Team Gon!
Oh my god!
Nice!
Huh?
I missed it!
What happened at the very end?
Total defeat.
Really?
So then Hisuka clinched it for us!
Or he stole our glory, but that depends on how you look at it.
We won because we all worked together.
That makes this a team victory.
You sound so out of character, Hisuka.
I lose.
As I promised, we'll all leave this town immediately.
Oh.
Yeah.
Well, that is what we wanted.
But first...
You asked about Jean, so I'll tell you.
You were so reckless!
It's no wonder your hands are all destroyed!
Are you even listening?!
To answer your question, Jean is not here.
And I don't know where he is.
Right.
Well, I kind of expected that.
But, I can tell you some old stories if you like.
Sure!
I am a convict on death row.
You see, I've murdered people.
Caught and incarcerated, sentenced to death.
Then Jean hired me to come here.
He taught me something important.
That if one person in this entire world believes in you,
just one,
you can be redeemed.
One day, my son's going to come here.
When he does, don't hold back!
Fine. Does that mean that I can kill him?
Don't underestimate him.
He is my kid.
I'm counting on you.
Thanks, Razor.
I always thought your dad was a little bit crazy.
Said he was making a game.
And the way he would talk about it for hours and hours on end
reminded me of an excited little kid or something.
Then he hired me, a condemned man, to fight his son.
You scum!
I hope you realize you owe me your life!
Hey!
You!
Over there!
What?
That thing?
I'm counting on you.
Thanks, Razor.
It felt like...
Like no one had ever called me by my name before.
Jean believed in your strength.
That's why he left you to me.
I believed in your strength too.
Which is why I didn't hold back.
Yeah.
But I couldn't have won without the help of everybody else.
That was great teamwork.
Yeah!
Now, go find Jean.
Okay!
Well, this is the place.
A window?
From this vantage point, we can see the shore.
So, how do we get to Poseidon's cavern from here?
Directly underneath that point, where the light shines.
You'll find an underground cavern.
But you won't find any treasure.
Because there isn't any.
I feel terrible for deceiving all of you.
There's no treasure?
We consider the cavern to be sacred, so only a few fishermen know exactly where it's located.
All of the other stories you've heard were just rumors that took on a life of their own.
But Razor and his pirate friends simply wouldn't believe us.
Those who live off the bounty of the sea can never defile it.
Or that's what they said, right before they were buried with their secrets.
Hey, don't forget, okay? It's just a story in a video game.
I can finally see the ocean again from here.
The rising sun.
The boats returning with their hauls.
All the colors sparkling across the water.
If you ask me, this is the greatest treasure of them all.
Yes! We finally got the strip of beach cart. Let's use clone. We gotta make two copies.
We're fine taking the copies.
Of course. You deserve to take the original.
Are you sure you don't want anything, Heizuka?
No, I've had enough fun.
Hey, why don't you stick around and join us?
I want to know what the troop is up to.
Oh, I'm not interested in collecting cards.
But contact me if anything else comes up.
I'll cast a company or magnetic force to fly over.
Huh? That jerk, he lied to us!
Huh? We haven't used magnetic force at all since Heizuka teamed up with us, am I right?
Uh-huh.
That means when he ran into us that he already knew about spell cards, get it?
Huh?
Killua, there are some liars who only lie when there's a good reason to, and then there are those who will lie without any reason at all.
You and I are the former, but Heizuka's the latter.
And fretting won't get you anywhere. Accept it.
Attention! Another player has cast contact on you.
It's been a while. Do you know who this is?
Get through!
What do you want?
First, I'd like to congratulate you.
What do you mean?
Aw, don't play dumb.
Don't play dumb.
So here's the deal. I promise to spare your lives, and you hand over the strip of beach in return.
That's ridiculous.
Well, I must admit I am somewhat interested to see if you can beat us.
If you're willing to make a deal, then come alone to Masadora's entrance gate in one hour. If you don't, we'll take the card by force.
Oh, and don't bother running or trying to hide. We have a lot of accompanies.
How? I knew you'd find out, but I never thought it would be so soon.
Asta, Amana, Mannheim, Nickyuu, Suhail, Kazu.
They were all members of your party of fifteen, correct?
If you'll just check your binder, you'll notice that they're no longer with us.
What?!
This means they're either dead, or they're not in the game anymore.
Get through!
Who are you?
I'm Gon Freaks, and I'm ready to take you on!
Gon, huh? So you're one of those three brats.
I see you have wild luck Alexandrite.
I'll find you when I'm done with Tezgera, unless you want to give up the card now.
Get over here right now! I want to fight you! I also have own!
Tezgera, talk somewhere else!
Attention, another player has cast contact on you.
This is Finks. We found him. We're heading in your direction as we speak.
Wouldn't it be faster to target the kids?
They probably don't have the original strip of beach, but I bet they got a copy.
If so, it would be a card created by Clone.
Yeah, you're right.
Once those kids see Tezgera surrender, they'll give up without a fight.
If we target the brats, Tezgera will have time to recover, which could be rather troublesome.
He's a single Star Hunter, after all. And we don't know what his ability is.
Genthru doesn't know what you're capable of.
He and his team assume that we have the original strip of beach.
And that could prove to be very helpful.
So they're after what they think is the original card.
The one we have.
We'll buy you as much time as possible. Use it to regain your strength.
If you want to beat this game, you'll have no choice but to fight them.
You're the only ones with a chance of beating them. There's no doubt in my mind.
But Gon, what you did just now was selfish.
But more than that, it was incredibly foolish.
If they had accepted your challenge and come, what would have happened to Kilowoc given the extent of his injuries?
By losing control of your emotions, you endangered not only yourself, but your friends too.
I'm really sorry.
That aside, it will all come down to a company. If we can stave off their pursuit, we should be able to buy plenty of time.
But if we let too much time pass, then they might just decide to change things and target you instead.
We probably have a week, more, and you're on your own.
One week. That's not very long. And to be honest, it's probably optimistic. They might even decide to focus on us after only three days or so.
Then I'll team up with Tezgera. What about you? What are you gonna do? If we're buying you time, that implies we have an alliance.
Wait. There's very little benefit in allying with them. Especially now that the enemy knows that the eight of us have been working together.
And that being the case, we won't be able to act as decoys while you take out Genthru.
So of course, we'll have to be careful with the two cards they still lack. Both number two and number 75.
Leaving them with any one party would be dangerous and we can't afford the risk.
That means that my offer to buy time isn't an alliance. What I'm offering you is a trade.
A trade, huh?
Just three weeks. That's all the time we can buy you. And if we succeed, you'll give us number 75, the Wild Luck Alexandrite card.
I don't get it. You just said you can only buy us a week.
Well, that's assuming that we stay on the run for that long. If necessary, I may be able to force a stalemate of sorts.
Oh, I see. But if you guys really want 75, we'll just tell you how you can get your hands on it.
No. We're well aware of how to obtain it. Some of us only have a few empty slots left, and that's including Gorenu.
We would be required to turn all of our cards over to the villagers, and that's no longer reasonable. Three weeks.
But that isn't nearly enough time for Kilawa's hands to heal, or to close the gap between our abilities and those of Genthru.
So, we should use that time to come up with a workable strategy.
Yes, exactly. Devise a scenario that you can win. Identify the circumstances, and then prepare to carry out the strategy.
We got it!
Good. We'll leave now and delay Team Genthru all we can. And never forget, Goren. They've killed over 50 players in this game so far.
If you truly want to beat the game, you'll have to fight them.
Accompany on! To Masadora!
Just three weeks? That sure isn't very much time.
Kilawa, you focus on healing. While you're doing that, think of a strategy to help us beat Genthru.
Right. Goren, you'll train with me. If we can just get you to where you can avoid his little flower, we'll be in good shape.
Us!
Goren has won his match against Razor, but the Bombers are still far more powerful than his group of allies.
Will they be able to find a path to success?
Oh
Coming up the great island tutorial
I